Once the protector get a connection from the any disc or RDP, so they can do more things
even they can open a command prompt and they can execute any commands in the machine.
And they can collect any information they want, they can open a browser and they can download
something.
So, they can basically they can do anything in the machine like a normal user.
Using this any disc will be little bit difficult because user does it, if it is a server,
if it is a server the user does it know what was actually happening behind that.
Even they can install any applications, any third-party software, they can do anything inside
the machine.
So, this is one of powerful techniques, very very strong techniques for our protectors to do
anything inside the machine.
So, in the next section we are going to collect some informations, collect some information
using any disc so the information is what we want silently.
So, now we are good with command and control section and we will see what are the other tools
that will be used for command and control by a protectors to achieve their C2C techniques.
So, let's hop off from here and we'll continue our discussion in the next video.
You guys, bye-bye.